completely separate. Okay. Right then, let's get started.
Hello ladies and welcome to our first goal set and workshop of the year. We
thought this would
be a good one to do obviously at the start of the year because I'm sure it's
like a it's a global
thing not going into the new year. People have all these like aspirations and
goals and new year's
resolutions. So I think it's a good one to start with as we can really just be
clear on what we want
and set a plan on how to get there.
Okay then.
So I thought we'd start off with a little exercise as it is the new year and I
feel like it's the
perfect time to set intentions to leave anything that is not saving us behind
back in 2022. Obviously
it's not the first day of the new year but that doesn't matter like if you know
it doesn't matter
if it's we're not doing it on the first day just as long as we've set the
intentions to leave it all
behind and move forward with new and like new stories that we're telling
ourselves
rather than the old ones that we're maybe holding us back. So we can all do
this now and I'd like
for us to write this down and so if you don't have a pen and paper you can go
and grab one now
quickly or just write it on an iPad or a phone or whatever it is you would
usually use but preferably
use pen and paper and maybe use a piece that you're only going to write this
this on because later on
after the call you can actually like do some things with the paper like maybe
bin it or something like that to symbolize like letting go of these things that
we're going to write
down. So firstly let's ask ourselves what do I need to let go of and what
limiting belief about
myself do I need to let go of and I thought as well what we can do is when we
're doing this
we can work with the energies of the current moon which is the waning moon and
I was reading
my book yesterday that for the waning moon and it's a wonderful phase for erad
icating anything
that may be causing problems or no longer saving us so it's like the perfect
time to be doing this
task and it says that you can cast spells or you know like do visualizations
and you know do
exercises for removing negative vibrations and clearly in a way any negative
energies so this
current moon phase is actually working with what we want to do with this
exercise so if you use it
into stuff like that we can use the energy of the moon to also help us let go
of these
of these things that we're not going to hold on to anymore and if you're into
crystals
the clear quart is a great one for this as well for like helping to like
manifest and like
you know manifest a new life that you want and not hold on to like any stuck
into energies
okay so we'll all do this now if that's okay we'll write down what we need to
let go of
and what limiting beliefs about ourselves that we need to let go of
spend a few minutes doing this
so
you
somebody else joining?
Hi Liz welcome and we're just doing a little exercise at the moment so if you
're ready to get
started just grab a pen and paper and write down on there what you need to let
go of
like what limiting beliefs about yourself that you need to let go of and
anything that you want
to leave behind in 2022 that is not coming into this new year with you because
it's not going to
save you in this year and so yeah just write down whatever that is that you
need to let go of
that's all we've done at the moment
you
okay then how's everyone getting on have you used on that yeah yeah yeah okay
perfect
does anybody want to share anything that they want to let go of
yeah I'll go first yeah I just want to I need to let go of this image I've got
about myself
um that um too old too far to this to that to go on camp because I really want
to do it
well I've just got this image and I just needed to get rid of it oh yeah
definitely because that
is not the case at all but I mean I was great when I first started I was all
fired up and then
obviously things happened and then when I was a last year they put some weight
on me and getting
it off but I just seem to have lost all my confidence now but being being on
the phones has been amazing
because I've been doing all kinds of scenarios but I just need to get rid of
this image I've got
about myself and that I can do it and that I am able to and that's really what
I've got to work on
yeah oh bless you but you know what honestly I I understand that's like as a
woman or just anyone
really in this in this society like in this world like it's hard isn't it
because
yeah we see all of these like perfect images or this or something yes not
even yeah
one it's not real and so everybody is perfect anyway like honestly like who
they are you know
and if you're a person that's all that matters and you are a people person you
know
and but well actually it's it's um we noticed that there's a couple of others
who are also
struggling with this um the same things as you lawner and we're going to do
yeah like a confidence
um workshop like it's like a Zoom call in february I think we're going to be
doing that one
so yeah hopefully that'll be a good one for you to come along to just focus on
like um
like summing that meat about edging in getting on to come and that and just
taking little steps
I mean I give myself little goals to the phones and stuff like that which is
really good and
seems to work even if they're just small um but it's just to ease me into this
so you know it's
the way I need to go to boost my earnings you know it's a lot of big right it's
just a little
confidence and just to get rid of this image I've got in my head of myself you
know let's share
yeah but you know what once you once you start going online and like once you
've done it like
a couple of times you know so different you know thank you you know yeah thanks
oh yeah I hope that
you get to let that go today and to be honest like I do these exercises and
like you know this
stuff like this about letting things go and welcoming in like just good things
and it takes
I've been also needing to let go like that's one of the things I wrote down was
um what is about my
like my body image and like my image as well and I've done these exercises so
many times but I feel
like the more I do it yet there's still a little bit of like like self doubt or
they saw that there
but honestly I feel I have come so far and I feel like it is like doing stuff
like this and just
visualising that like leaving my body you know and although I'm not 100% there
yet I feel like I'm
a lot than I ever was so I do feel like this does help so it'll be great our
own pressure don't we
that we shouldn't do you know for this perfection and nobody's really bothered
I suppose you know
in the end but it's just for me just getting the confidence to get these little
steps done and
I'm sure I'll be fine but I've got to get rid of these things I've got in my
own head
okay so maybe today you can get a bit of paper that you've wrote on I've taken
mine out of my
paint my book and I'm gonna I'm gonna go and bend it and as I'm bending it I'm
just gonna feel like
I'm letting go of that like one final time you know when it's gone so we can
maybe
all do that later obviously we'll do it right now and but after the call if you
just keep
your bit of paper that you wrote on you can go with it or something thank you
okay thanks for
sharing on lawner does anybody else want to share before we go on to the next
the next thing
no yeah I can hear you hi hey um so yeah I guess like my one um I've kind of
already done like a
new year workshop which was setting intentions so I love all this stuff I think
goals are really
practical um like small goals and long-term goals but um when you said like
what do I need
to let go of I just sort of like fear like that was the first thing that popped
into my head was
just like fear and that in congress is like everything like fear of fear of
like um
discomfort fear of stepping out of my comfort zone fear of failure yeah yeah
just like just
fear in general just like letting go of that and just yeah like stepping into
my power um but yeah
oh nice thank you for sharing that um but yeah I feel you're like fear of not
being a new comfort
zone like yeah that can be scary but then that's also a place where like you
grow and like
learn so much about yourself and um yeah so that's a good one to let go of for
sure
so yeah thank you for sharing yeah does anybody else want to share yeah can I
share yeah sure um
so mine's more physical sort of thing obviously I've got body issues as well
you know
but mainly I need to actually physically like now have a lot of stuff always
mean a bit of a
whole day my heart is a bit of a whole day and now we've got to move house like
as soon as possible
we want to stay in this area so we're going to have to downsize
be able to afford it so we just need to lack out of stuff and sometimes I can
be ruthless
and just lash it in bags to go to the trash shop just lash it lash it lash it
and sometimes like
oh but that's that ticket to that play that I saw 20 years ago oh that's that t
-shirt that
I bought at the top of the friggin empire state building 15 years yeah but I
thought of an idea
today all my t-shirts I never wear that I've got the like band t-shirts and I'm
going to cut them
all off and make them into a quilt oh so yeah I was just thinking that so yeah
oh god jack I think
that'll look really cool yeah so it'll be one big quilt rather than big proud t
-shirts but you know
um but I am just going to be ruthless take everything to the trash shop doesn't
save me
doesn't have you know any use it's not beautiful last three four five times I
've moved I'm just
carrying this bags of stuff with me that haven't really even looked in again so
it's all just
got to go so I am physically going to let go and yeah I like being that as well
as the frigging
piece of paper honestly I feel yeah like when you let go of stuff you just feel
so much lighter
don't you know and I feel like stuff it's just stress like honestly like with
moving country so
many times I've been like oh my god now I've got to go through all of this
stuff to take with me
or just get rid of all this or that and like when you get when you let go
overall you just feel like
a lot lighter so yeah you'll feel great so and I feel yeah like it's nice to
keep all of the things
that maybe you know oh this reminds me of this and this and that but if you're
just in a bag in
your house and you've not even looked at it and god knows how many years or
whatever else then
do you really need it you know that's why I asked myself so yeah I can't wait
for this
you'll feel a lot lighter after the first shot yeah but yeah that's a good one
okay then did anybody
us want to share before we um before we move on
I'd like to say hello to everybody oh hello dear I'm the newest person probably
here and the oldest
and yeah maybe I think I am
whoops how you doing lost you no no well and um well one of them ladies has
said exactly what I
thought I've got body problems and uh of myself and yeah all my friends say
absolutely the opposite
but I'm taking action I've joined the gym I've lost seven pounds and you know I
'm taking positive
action to get my body back where it was my life I live in a motorhome oh yeah
nice
amazing yeah so I had to downsize as you can imagine I wanted to live in a
motorhome at one point
yeah I live in a motorhome I've traveled all around the uk and now I found a a
brilliant job but um
it gives me like somewhere free to stay free to use electric free to use the
laundry and I work
in the office so this is in the my job is in the evenings you know doing the um
the cam work
but I haven't got the confidence at the moment I thought I had and then when I
started I don't know
my confidence waned and uh my friend said to me I don't know why she said
because she thinks I'm
great but I don't what's your name sorry it's jad'sn't come off on me okay okay
yeah
hi hi hi thanks for coming on thank you and some lady has been helping me is it
you
no she's just done my profile today who's done that would be is that our admin
that's probably our
admin wow I tell you I'm so happy I feel like somebody's there
you know I feel like people are in my court oh that's sammy yes yeah I mean you
're like
part of a family you know yeah the cam fan yeah the cam fan and I I'm totally
on my own I have no
family I've got friends um never married never had children just me and the dog
in the motorhome
but it's not down the globe it's good you know I'm happy so yeah this is my
yeah I've just got to
get this all sorted out where I'm confident and I'm actually earn and then away
I go yeah then the
rest of my dreams come because I want to get a boat and live on a boat as well
I would love to live
on a boat that would be amazing well if you do that we'll get to see your
journey that's what
happens yeah yeah yeah you know if they're dreams yeah you don't think
can I say something about the body stuff um my own experience which I don't
know might be
helpful or not can you hear me yes yeah um so before I started I think you guys
all know that
us but I started dancing really young like fought into sex work and I was 18 19
and before that I
had like a crippling eating disorder right and the most terrible terrible body
to small fear
and I found that getting into sex work whether it was like validation from
other people or just
seeing my body as a tool and how it could serve me really really helped me with
my um body confidence
and like I said it was less so from like people telling you oh you're gorgeous
you're gorgeous
but it was more about like looking at your body in a different way and feeling
more connected to it
and like your sensuality so I don't know I always think that it's if you're
nervous you might actually
feel differently after you've tried it and it might be quite positive and go
great thank you
yeah and I was thinking about the body confidence um with me I was I was
conscious about my body but
I just started to make it a unique uh me smart on the camp and I'm actually
getting um all the
work right if that makes sense so to do that to the advantage yeah we were
talking about this um
with the mentors me and jay how some people are getting discouraged because
they're thinking
that they're not getting calls because of their image or their body or whatever
but actually it's
because of you know their profile needs more work or they're you know they're
not selling smells
in the right way or whatever so yeah we're gonna we'll do a lot more about that
in our body confidence
call that's coming up um actually there doesn't it how many hours are you meant
to put in
per week rastly to be honest that that's that's entirely up to the individual
some people have a
lot more time to put into this some don't but I would say honestly in the
beginning especially
when you're trying to build yourself up just as much time as you've got like if
you've if you
wake a full-time job then of course you know just after work or if you're just
only waking up part
time the day that you're not in work spend online your profile or um but yeah
we'll we'll um we've
actually got stuff on the on the members area which can help with with regard
to how you do your
profile up and stuff like that because that's something that's quite important
um we feel and
like rel just said it's not you're not not getting calls because of how you
look you're probably not
getting calls because your profile is completely basic and does not look
exciting to the client
so it's a really important thing to get your profile up and amazing and trust
me the calls
will be coming through and we've got we've got the webcam call training call
Zoom call
is it next thursday um the 19 so anyone who's like any of that stuff comes back
call and we'll go
through loads of useful stuff then yeah okay um let me see yeah it's next fizz
day iapm yeah amazing
okay um and we'll move on now on to the next slide and but what you said jess
was really
really helpful and if anybody else has got any little tips about what they do
to have more body
confidence or just confidence in general and if you come along to the the call
and you can share
your tips in there as well if you would like to that would be great um because
then it'll be on
the members area for everyone to see um okay if you want to sort of um catch up
with me I'm
lorna and then we can sort of part they're up together and help each other
maybe I would love
to lorna I would love to together golden order you have how do you contact one
another though um
well I'll put a message in the groove and then just contact me there then yeah
yeah that'd be great
all right darling yeah oh that'd be lovely yeah that's nice yeah that's nice
okay then let's move on
oh the picture of the moon didn't show this whole time
okay then so now that we've got into a good mindset and like we've left out of
the things
that are no longer savours let's take a look at what we want for this year
okay so compassionate goal setting so this one is going to be a little bit
different to previous ones that we've done previous goal setting workshops
usually we do like the smart goals and we're really focused on you know setting
like setting a plan for what we're going to do and even though we're still
going to do that today
um we're going to take a look at compassionate goal setting because sometimes
things don't always
go to plan or you know things come up and we put too much pressure on ourselves
and then that could
actually be just a downward spiral and then we don't set we don't achieve
anything because we're
just in not the best heads base so I think it's good that when we are setting
goals and
working towards them that we'd be compassionate with ourselves as well and so
these are the
six steps that we're going to go through today okay so step one identify what
we want
okay so grab your pen and paper and we're going to write down three goals that
we want to achieve
this year and then afterwards and we're going to write next to each one so
leave a bit of space
how we will feel when we've achieved these goals so like I said earlier we're
just going to do
free and then if you want to go back later and do it with all the rest of the
goals that you've
got this year maybe you've got a lot more free um or maybe you've only just got
one or two which
is fine like you know I'm just do whatever it is good for you and this can be
like
as we're going to be doing just free we can look at the bigger the bigger goals
that we've got so
say you've just got little like small ones that can be done over the next
day or so maybe leave them ones off for the moment and just focus on the big
ones that we've got
for the whole year okay so we'll spend a couple of minutes writing this down
now
so
you
think as well like when I was putting this together I read a couple of things
that was saying when you're
setting um goals for the year like obviously some common ones could be like I
don't know
get a new car or a new house or I don't know like big things like that that is
um obviously
stuff that you have to work hard towards but then also I mean I'm and that's
great of course and I'm
sure like I'm sure when you achieve that that feels amazing but then also I
think it's good to
like set like creative goals that keep you like keep you like in your creative
energy and maybe
doing something new that you've never done before or like letting your inner
child play so for example
maybe you know we've wanted to to learn by a dance and say I don't know that
just comes to
me head on see because this is what I'm doing now but then you just think other
things are getting
in the way like the bigger thing is like oh but I need to get a car or a new
type of house
I think it's good to have time and make time for stuff like that that's
creative and fun and
keeps you in a child's happy you know so maybe there's something like that that
we forgot to to
do for ourselves and yeah it's obviously good to do the important stuff you
know but then also
stuff like this I feel like it's just important to just keep your keep your
phone and fresh and
happy and not just like working hard towards like these big things you know
so yeah maybe that's something to think about as well for one of the girls this
year
so
okay how's everyone getting on I've been
once everyone wrote down three goals and how they're going to feel one
statement yes yeah
okay yeah does anybody want to share maybe one or two of their goals um I don't
mind sharing
yeah sure thank you yeah so I've put actually mine mine was creative on them um
I wrote
that I want to put a performance piece together a dance piece and perform it at
sex quiz at this
year oh nice and feeling wise how I think I will feel that was it right how
will I feel yeah um
I wrote here uh I feel self-reliance in in control of my medium and having done
that I will feel
clearer having a new physical way to communicate oh nice um and then the other
one I put um
I'd like to save 70,000 pounds
and then I put chair um our full motivator continue um I'll also feel calmer in
my decisions to
stay in sex work um and I will feel in more in control and like less kind of
like fragile
which t washing yeah having yeah because I want to buy a flat so that's the
financial goal for
this year for the flat so oh nice amazing I love that and I'm sure that they'll
go hand in hand
like doing your performance will allow you to make more money to save so um so
yeah perfect
thank you for sharing dear thank you so anybody else want to share
well one of mine is to live a life because I think this work can be very uh
lonely
do a great it can be a very lonely life and for a few years I have been lonely
because I used to do
actual um physically see people and I spent my time doing that as well as
trying to hold a job
down my life went very much upside down over the last few years but now I'm in
a place where I'm
close to friends for the first time and I've never gone out so much I've been
to the theater
I've been to the cinema and I'm actually living a life which is a happy balance
which is making me happier in myself to go forward and save money work and do
you know my
other jobs are like the cam work and everything so yeah that's so important
yeah especially the
late nights and stuff you can literally go months without like doing anything
for yourself and not
yeah yeah I think like every goal should involve pleasure at some point
yeah otherwise it's just not attainable is it not sustainable but it is a
lonely business don't
you stink I think it can be any type of work is busy very lonely yeah I agree I
think it can be
especially if you are doing in-person stuff because it's got such bad hours but
I think um
I struggle with that for super long time but also branching out and having
other sex
worker friends kind of is also a nice way around that because you guys will
often be on the same
schedules and you understand each other exactly you can talk openly you're not
hiding anything
I like having friends that are sex workers and like I slightly say normal
friends because I like
having I feel like the job that we do is that it's like cataboo in society and
a lot of people
and they don't understand it so I have my sex worker friends that I can go to
and talk about all
this crazy shit that goes on but then I like to have my like friends who just
are like teachers
and normal stuff like that and then just just have like a some normal seat if
that makes sense
yeah I do I think since lockdown as well I mean I work from home in miday job
as well and
we're all over the country I work with a group of people we we never met but we
have our own little
support probably like five or six of us on the team and yeah I have to be
careful because I can go
right through Monday to Friday that you've gone out the house it's like stupid
yeah you know and
this is it you're right you have to start booking things and this is where I'm
looking at and
out booking things to go places do things and that otherwise you just your life
passes your
vibes all of it you know try and find the work like uh the work social life
balance yeah exactly
meet your friends working try and find a balance yeah that's all I have to say
it's like it's either
that or you feel like you're chasing money all the time yes and I don't I don't
want to feel like
that I want to live my life yeah especially being at the latter part of my life
I think that's the
beauty of what we do though that you can you know we're not with this is not
like a capsule it we
can step outside of capitalism for a little bit and we can actually work our
work around our lives
quite funny I'll be doing something like because I audit cases and stuff like
mortgage cases they're
like oh sometimes I get a bit federal and then I'll get a call I'll have a
right laugh and a giggle
and then I just go back on to check in this case it's really quite fun you know
I think
another really good way to manage that is um that I only learned like fuck last
year
is scheduling in things like schedule in your pleasure because once you've
bought the tickets
and you've made the plans yeah it's hard to back out with and then you know you
do yeah yeah for
yourself exactly I mean I started this year first of January I went to the
theatre so I started
this year and I'm loving it all right that's nice okay yeah everyone I love to
hear from everyone
and what's going on because it's nice because then we can be inspired from each
other you know
yeah it's because some other people's goals can suddenly you know and like you
become your
girls as well because you don't really know what they are don't they know
exactly exactly yeah
um okay then so now that we've um identified what we want we can list the
action steps
so we're going to do two um two different things for each goal so for each one
we're going to
take a look at what we can do this week to get started so say for example your
goal is to save
um a significant amount of money like jess is an also like one of mine
something that I could do
this week could be to um write out a plan of okay so by the end of February I
should have this
much saved by the end of July I should be this much or something like that that
's something
I can do this week obviously I'm or I'm not going to save all the money this
week but I can make a
plan of how much I should save um or I can set up a savings account or
something like that so
so yeah what can you do this week to get started on your goals and we're also
going to create a
deadline timeline for the year so say for example you know that one year goals
it's you know
it's not going to be a full year one you could write down like you know by July
this will be done
and then you can create like deadlines and check in with yourself so every
month or so like okay
so that by this month I should have done this much progress towards the goal by
this month I
should be this much closer um so yeah you get the gist so just go through the
three goals and just
do this for each one please
so
okay how's everyone getting on is everyone from this
yeah yeah okay we'll move on to the um the next the next steps for if you still
need more time on
this one you can just um catch it back up later on
okay so the final thing that we're going to do to help us um get closer to our
goals is to create
helpful habits oh okay so what can you start doing daily that'll bring you
closer to your goals
so I feel like doing like you know changing your everyday routine
is something that will ultimately change your life you know like just
implementing something new
a day like something even something little um that you never done before and if
you're doing that
every single day it's going to end up changing everything so um so yeah I think
this is a very
good one um to do to like implement now that we've got new goals
so um so yeah if we go back through our three goals and then right next to each
one what a habit
that we can do daily um is that will help us get closer to that so for example
one of my goals
and involves yoga something to do with yoga so of course my daily habit would
be to practise
every single day which is something that I don't do anymore and so I need to
get back to that so
that's definitely what I'm going to do for that one
so yeah we'll spend a few minutes doing this
so
okay how's everyone getting on with that was everyone wrote down um some daily
habits that we're
going to start implementing um yeah yeah I have okay does anybody want to share
any of their
habits that they're going to start doing daily and they say don't think that it
takes about
21 days to create a habit so so yeah if we start doing that
yeah sure so for my first goal I cut it's it's really hard because my first
goal is to
move in with me all by the end of the year um so really daily it's already
planned we're planning
on getting all the help for anything up to date before we start moving in so I
can't really put
anything for that because I don't know what I can do daily for that number two
is to start
coming again um I've been on I went on last night it was really quiet for me I
think I've been bought
I haven't been on so that's expected and then number three is to lose weight so
maybe better
choice is with food start exercising again and just start cooking for myself
again because I don't
have been a motivation to cook because I've not really got an appetite but I
need to eat stuff
okay nice thank you for sharing to yeah um so you said that you wanted to move
out but then
you're not really sure what habits you could do daily that um the help with
that what I just
face for whatever I mean I don't know if it's really a habit or just something
that you could do
every day you could like go online or something or even stores when you're out
and about and like
pick things for your new house you know what I mean like and then I've been all
started with
I've already got all that I've got before oh oh I want my kitchen what I want
my bathroom
I would joke for my kitchen window and everything so oh nice they already know
what I want it's just
yeah executing it because I've got a dorm and shopping and everything with Neil
he's
he's got to say he's got to like it as well not just not just me because it's
all right I'm saying
yeah he's gonna buy me the kitchen but I can't say if he's going to be living
in that kitchen more
than I am so but I've got all my plans and everything for all that I know I'm
on there every day for
inspiration oh yeah I've got all that already amazing yeah and I'm sure that
like as you like
you know you're looking at the stuff that you want and it's in that like it's
just more like
manifesting and actually being real you know what I mean yeah so yeah nice
thank you for sharing
do yeah does anybody else want to share before we head on to the next the next
slide
I've got a good saving scheme which I heard which I'm following um as you know
there's 30 or 31
days in a month you can either do this with like um I'm with either a penny if
you save a penny on
the first two on the second three on the third four on the fourth five on the
fifth if you keep
going like that and at the end of the month you start a penny again on the
first and so forth
by the end of the year the six hundred and sixty seven six hundred and sixty
seven pounds saved
oh but if I I'm doing it with a pound so I love six thousand six hundred and
seventy
five saved or how is something around that figure anyway yeah so it's a good
way to
save because you can set it to your own goal either a penny fifty p or a pound
yeah exactly and I'm
sure we've all got a penny to spare at least and then if you can pay a fact
because then
of course you wouldn't even more saved yeah that's a good one I like that one
thank you for sharing
that yeah um okay then so we'll move on to the next slide and the final one um
okay oh would anyone
like to share we've already done that okay so number four on compassionate goal
setting is
checking in with yourself so we've already wrote down um a deadline like the
deadline timeline for
each goal so you know by this date I should be this much progress in I should
have this much saved
or I should you know I should have been this much closer or whatever it is that
we're doing um
when we when we've got our deadlines and we're checking you know our progress
with the goal
it's also good to check like checking with ourselves as well and like how we're
feeling how
it's been going you know if we're putting too much pressure on ourselves or
maybe if we're not you
know if we're not like taking it seriously as much and we need to like put more
energy into it and
so yeah obviously this isn't something that we're going to do today or maybe
you can write it down
on your um on your timelines for the year so when you are checking in with the
goal of how far
you've came with the goal you can also check in with yourself as well um so
yeah I think that's
nice to do let me just see what else I've wrote down here yeah so basically um
and just don't
obviously put too much pressure on yourself like obviously we want to achieve
our goals
but at the same time we don't want to be put on all this unnecessary pressure
on ourselves
and then we're just not happy in the process because it's good to achieve of
course and we
will want to achieve but we don't want to have an unhappy life in the process
of
like you know achieving like we want to be happy in the in the build up to
achieve in it as well you
know okay and number five is a love for self-compassion um so obviously
unpredictable things can happen
in life so you know you might have a goal set and then something comes up and
completely froze
you off course and then you know you don't end up achieving that goal by the
time you wanted to
um and that's okay you know like things happen um you know something else might
come up that
became becomes more important or requires your attention more than whatever the
goal is um
and that's okay you know like yeah we want to achieve but we also don't want to
be
ourselves up if if things get in the way of that so obviously once again this
is not something
that to do today but just bear in mind you know in the future um to allow for
self-compassion
and finally number six modify the plan so
so when we look back and we're checking in um how far we've came with our goals
and how our
progress is how we're feeling um maybe then we realise oh actually I'm not
where I thought I was
going to be right now I'm not where I plan to be right now I've still got a
couple of more things
that I need to do before I get closer to the goal um or before I achieve it and
that's fine like
if you're not you know not on the same you're not following them your deadline
fully like if
you're a little bit behind that's fine so that just means we just have to
modify it a little bit and
and then um and go from there you know or maybe you've got there quicker than
your force and you
actually already have achieved the goal and I think this is a nice time to
celebrate it you know
because we put all this pressure on ourselves well hopefully we're not going to
do that but
maybe we you know we've worked hard to like get there and then once we're there
we don't even
celebrate that we've actually done that so um I think it's nice to to celebrate
our wins you know
because I think we're quick to judge ourselves when we mess up or this or that
um but we don't
actually sit for a moment and celebrate the fact that we've worked hard and we
've achieved something
really amazing um so yeah obviously like I said these are the things that we'll
do in the future
um but it's good to just have on your on your notes just so if so when we do
check in and look back
that we remember to allow for self-compassion modify the plan and to check in
with ourselves
okay then so that brings us to the end of this um this workshop
does anybody want to share anything from you know maybe um stuff that we
achieved last year that
maybe you forgot to really you know shout about it and celebrate the fact that
you achieved that
or maybe you want to share some of the goals that you've got for this year
or maybe not maybe we've shared enough okay okay then darlings well
this is um this brings us to the end of our workshop thank you for coming along
everyone
it's nice to see some new faces and see the tenant faces um oh what have I done
here sorry
just stop sharing my screen okay great how's everyone doing
thank you thank you so much thank you I'd like to contact me I don't know how
she is going to
are you in the group are you in the WhatsApp group yes yeah okay she can send a
message in there
maybe and you can connect yeah very good and and newbies that have been on the
call tonight
it'd be great if you can come to our website